Guide to the Tuol Sleng confessions and photographs, 1991-1993
Tuol Sleng confessions and photographs, 1991-1993
- Series I. Confessions A-H (No F or G), Dates are formatted as Day/Month/Year
  - Names: C
    - Chhun Sithân, 8/8/1978 (Reel 14, Frame 6)
      Dates of Confessions: 24/8/1977
    - Chhun Sos, 19/7/1978 (Reel 16, Frame 25)
    - Chhun Srou, N/A (Reel 8, Frame 2)
      Dates of Confessions: 1/11/1976
    - Chhunh Soeurn, 2/11/1977 (Reel 18, Frame 26)
      Dates of Confessions: 4/12/1977; 11/11/1977
    - Chhuon, N/A (Reel 22, Frame 4)
      Dates of Confessions: 8/5/1977
    - Chhuon Khoeun, 6/1977 (Reel 8, Frame 3)
      Dates of Confessions: 13/9/1977
    - Chhuon Khoeurn, N/A (Reel 13, Frame 2)
      Dates of Confessions: 28/9/1977
    - Chhuon Man, 23/9/1975 (Reel 19, Frame 8)
      Dates of Confessions: 8/10/1975
    - Chhuon Nhey, 7/1977 (Reel 17, Frame 17)
      Dates of Confessions: 1/8/1977; 21/8/1977
    - Chhuon Oeurn, 17/9/1977 (Reel 23, Frame 12)
      Dates of Confessions: 15/11/1977
    - Chhuon Sarin, 10/5/1977 (Reel 20, Frame 46)
      Dates of Confessions: 20/5/1977; 22/1/1978; 28/3/1978
    - Chhuon Sarou, 25/11/1976 (Reel 22, Frame 7)
      Dates of Confessions: 4/3/1977; 1/3/1977; 3/1977
    - Chhuon Svang, 18/8/1977 (Reel 22, Frame 3)
      Dates of Confessions: 15/9/1977; 9/10/1977
    - Chhuon Thuong, 3/1978 (Reel 18, Frame 4)
    - Chhuorn Phat, N/A (Reel 18, Frame 17)
      Dates of Confessions: 14/1/1977
    - Chhy Hey, 4/7/1977 (Reel 10, Frame 3)
      Dates of Confessions: 26/9/1977
    - Chhy Hor, 25/3/1978 (Reel 7, Frame 14)
      Dates of Confessions: 24/4/1978; 2 sections undated
    - Chien Chea, N/A (Reel 12, Frame 3)
    - Chim Bun, 28/5/1977 (Reel 8, Frame 10)
      Dates of Confessions: 28/5/1977
    - Chim Choeurn, 11/8/1976 (Reel 22, Frame 16)
      Dates of Confessions: 11/8/1976
    - Chim Chun, N/A (Reel 12, Frame 4)
      Dates of Confessions: 24/2/1978
    - Chim Doeurn, N/A (Reel 18, Frame 6)
      Dates of Confessions: 29/5/1977
    - Chim Hor, 19/1/1978 (Reel 20, Frame 37)
      Dates of Confessions: 19/1/1978
    - Chim Sos, 1/1978 (Reel 17, Frame 12)
    - Chim Van Coeng (Cang) (Lê Vann Phu’o’e), 6/5/1976 (Reel 187, Frame 8)
    - Chim Van Youp (Lê Van Mai), 6/5/1976 (Reel 187, Frame 7)
    - Chim Vann (Kaeu) Cu, 6/5/1975 (Reel 187, Frame 6)
    - Chin Chhamu, 7/2/1978 (Reel 23, Frame 9)
      Dates of Confessions: 29/2/1978; 7/2/1978
    - Chin Chhang, N/A (Reel 14, Frame 2)
      Dates of Confessions: 4/5/1977; 21/4/1977; 1/5/1977; 16/5/1977; 21/5/1977; 22/4/1977; 23/4/1977; 15/4/1977; 28/3/1977; 25/3/1977
      26/3/1977; 24/3/1977; 24/3/1977; 24/3/1977; 8/4/1977; 21/2/1977
      8/4/1977; 29/4/1977; 20/2/1977
    - Chin Doriyan, 14/8/1977 (Reel 16, Frame 17)
      Dates of Confessions: 20/8/1977
    - Chin Ear, 3/1977 (Reel 21, Frame 34)
      Dates of Confessions: 2/6/1977; 4/5/1977
    - Chin Eng, 20//6/1977 (Reel 16, Frame 20)
      Dates of Confessions: 8/9/1977; 20/9/1977; 5/11/1977
    - Chin Ho, 21/8/1977 (Reel 19, Frame 3)
      Dates of Confessions: 28/9/1977; 1 section no date
    - Chin Hoeurn, 6/3/1976 (Reel 19, Frame 15)
    - Chin Ney, 1/1976 (Reel 13, Frame 11)
      Dates of Confessions: 3/8/1977
    - Chin Phal, 28/2/1976 (Reel 20, Frame 2)
    - Chin Phon, 2/1978 (Reel 20, Frame 33)
    - Chin Poleap, N/A (Reel 7, Frame 16)
      Dates of Confessions: 19/9/1976; 20/9/1976; 21/9/1976; 22/9/1976
    - Chin Ren, 11/1/1976 (Reel 12, Frame 13)
    - Chin Ry, 4/2/1977 (Reel 19, Frame 17)
      Dates of Confessions: 12/1976; 1/1/1977; 4/2/1977
    - Chin Sovath, 26/10/1976 (Reel 5, Frame 2)
      Age: 51
      Dates of Confessions: 17/10/1976; 19/10/1976; 20/10/1976; 21/10/1976; 22/10/1976; 24/10/1976; 26/10/1976; 2/11/1976
      3/11/1976; 5/11/1976; 27/12/1976
    - Chin Sun Leng, 24/4/1975 (Reel 20, Frame 13)
      Dates of Confessions: 28/4/1975; 13/12/1975
    - Chin Tai Heng, 2/7/1977 (Reel 18, Frame 27)
      Dates of Confessions: 10/8/1977; 23/8/1977; 7/9/1977
    - Chin Thol, 9/1/1977 (Reel 22, Frame 18)
      Dates of Confessions: 29/1/1977; 20/1/1977; 21/1/1977
    - Chin Thy, 16/2/1978 (Reel 16, Frame 28)
      Dates of Confessions: 18/3/1978
    - Chin Uth, 2/9/1977 (Reel 19, Frame 28)
      Dates of Confessions: 17/9/1977
    - Chin Vorn, 17/6/1977 (Reel 8, Frame 6)
      Dates of Confessions: 17/6/1977
    - Ching Chhun Leang, 18/10/1976 (Reel 4, Frame 42)
      Dates of Confessions: 6/1/1977; 7/1/1977;8/1/1977; 9/1/1977; 11/1/1977; 12/1/1977
    - Chip Lak, N/A (Reel 19, Frame 6)
    - Chlang San, N/A (Reel 18, Frame 13)
      Dates of Confessions: 12/2/1977
    - Choeng Thann Hoeurng, 6/5/1976 (Reel 187, Frame 12)
    - Choeng Ve·, N/A (Reel 7, Frame 6)
    - Choeu Vuth, 23/10/1977 (Reel 13, Frame 32)
      Dates of Confessions: 18/2/1977; 20/2/1977; 17/2/1977
    - Choeung Py, 15/8/1978 (Reel 14, Frame 7)
      Dates of Confessions: 9/9/1978
    - Chon You Meng, 8/2/1977 (Reel 20, Frame 48)
      Dates of Confessions: 11/3/1977; 20/2/1977; 25/2/1977(6)
    - Chor Chhan, 27/2/1977 (Reel 12, Frame 25)
      Dates of Confessions: 4/3/1977; 9/3/1977; 5/3/1977; 11/3/1977; 12/3/1977; 21/2/1977; 19/2/1977; 1/3/1977; 3/4/1977
      24/3/1977; 23/3/1977; 4/3/1977; 13/3/1977; 16/3/1977(2); 23/3/1977; 27/3/1977
      3/4/1977; 17/3/1977; 14/3/1977; 4/4/1977; 28/2/1977; 5/4/1977; 18/3/1977
      16/3/1977; 4/4/1977; 19/3/1977; 18/3/1977; 4/3/1977; 3/3/1977
    - Chor Hong, N/A (Reel 23, Frame 25)
      Dates of Confessions: 18/6/1977
    - Chor Try, 12/1/1976 (Reel 18, Frame 42)
      Age: 53
    - Chorn Chhay, 12/4/1978 (Reel 20, Frame 19)
      Dates of Confessions: 26/4/1978
    - Chorn Pik, 2/1978 (Reel 18, Frame 31)
    - Chort Soth, 21/5/1977 (Reel 17, Frame 25)
      Dates of Confessions: 13/9/1977; 2 sections undated
    - Chot Nhe, N/A (Reel 11, Frame 17)
    - Chou Chet, N/A (Reel 12, Frame 22)
      Age: 52
      Dates of Confessions: 2/5/1978; 9/5/1978; 20/5/1978; 20/5/1978(2); 21/5/1978; 27/5/1978
    - Chou Chun Horn, 28/8/1978 (Reel 23, Frame 30)
      Dates of Confessions: 11/10/1977
    - Chou Kan, 28/11/1975 (Reel 23, Frame 14)
      Dates of Confessions: 4/12/1975; 14/12/1975; 19/12/1975
    - Chou Kim, 28/10/1978 (Reel 21, Frame 28)
      Dates of Confessions: 5/11/1978; 16/11/1978; 25/11/1978; 26/11/1978
    - Chou Mang, 1/8/1977 (Reel 19, Frame 23)
      Dates of Confessions: 14/10/1977; 18/8/1977
    - Chou Ni, N/A (Reel 23, Frame 13)
      Dates of Confessions: 13/7/1977
    - Chou Prin, N/A (Reel 22, Frame 1)
    - Chou The, 2/5/1977 (Reel 20, Frame 11)
      Dates of Confessions: 2/5/1977
    - Chou Vang Le, 3/1978 (Reel 187, Frame 25)
    - Choum Lach, N/A (Reel 8, Frame 4)
      Dates of Confessions: 11/4/1977; 11/4/1977; 11/4/1977
    - Chour Ron, N/A (Reel 18, Frame 5)
    - Chrek Ros, N/A (Reel 19, Frame 35)
      Age: 38
      Dates of Confessions: 20/10/1975
    - Christopher Edward Delance, 26/11/1978 (Reel 185, Frame 52)
      Nationality (if foreign): United States (CIA)
    - Chrung San, N/A (Reel 5, Frame 10)
      Dates of Confessions: 23/9/1975; 1 section undated
    - Chu Chay, 11/1/1977 (Reel 22, Frame 21)
      Dates of Confessions: 8/3/1977; 17/2/1977; 5/3/1977
    - Chuan Sao, N/A (Reel 19, Frame 2)
      Dates of Confessions: 24/3/1977
    - Chuch Chandy, N/A (Reel 8, Frame 13)
    - Chuch Phay, 25/11/1977 (Reel 20, Frame 8)
      Dates of Confessions: 2/12/1977
    - Chum Bonadeth, N/A (Reel 22, Frame 12)
      Dates of Confessions: 29/4/1977
    - Chum Cheam, N/A (Reel 19, Frame 4)
      Dates of Confessions: 2/5/1977; 3/4/1977; 25/3/1977
    - Chum Choeurn, 6/10/1976 (Reel 12, Frame 1)
      Dates of Confessions: 27/10/1976; 30/10/1976 (2) 10/11/1976; 15/11/1976; 13/11/1976; 28/10/1976
    - Chum Chorn, 7/2/1978 (Reel 19, Frame 12)
    - Chum Diep, N/A (Reel 16, Frame 11)
    - Chum Khyan, N/A (Reel 22, Frame 20)
      Dates of Confessions: 20/11/1976; 19/11/1976; 22/11/1976; 21/11/1976; 20/11/1976; 15/11/1976(6); 17/11/1976
      19/11/1976(4); 1/12/1976; 20/11/1976; 2/12/1976(4); 18/11/1976
    - Chum Manh, 28/10/1978 (Reel 16, Frame 8)
      Dates of Confessions: 6/11/1978
    - Chum Neang, N/A (Reel 6, Frame 12)
      Dates of Confessions: 24/2/1977; 22/2/1977; 23/2/1977; 25/2/1977
    - Chum Penh, 17/8/1977 (Reel 18, Frame 34)
      Dates of Confessions: 24/8/1977; 23/10/1977
    - Chum Pha, 24/3/1978/ (Reel 18, Frame 20)
      Dates of Confessions: 24/7/1978
    - Chum Phal, N/A (Reel 20, Frame 15)
      Dates of Confessions: 28/11/1975
    - Chum Ran, 4/10/1976 (Reel 21, Frame 1)
      Dates of Confessions: 21/9/1976; 26/9/1976
    - Chum Saing, 28/1/1978 (Reel 20, Frame 43)
    - Chum San, 3/2/1978 (Reel 23, Frame 21)
      Dates of Confessions: 9/2/1978
    - Chum Savath, 31/7/58 (Reel 18, Frame 15)
      Dates of Confessions: 13/9/1975
    - Chum Savon, 17/9/1976 (Reel 14, Frame 8)
      Dates of Confessions: 23/9/1976; 24/9/1976; 25/9/1976; 25/9/1976; 26/9/1976; 27/9/1976; 2/10/1976
      3/10/1976; 4/9/1976; 5/9/1976; 7/10/1976; 7/10/1976; 19/10/1976
      8/9/1976; 18/10/1976; 1 section undated
    - Chum Thai Y, 17/2/1977 (Reel 10, Frame 6)
      Dates of Confessions: 5/3/1977; 9/3/1977; 9/3/1977
    - Chum Thy, N/A (Reel 23, Frame 23)
      Dates of Confessions: 13/5/1977
    - Chum Yeth, 20/5/1977 (Reel 14, Frame 4)
      Dates of Confessions: 17/9/1977; 31/3/1977; 1 section undated
    - Chun, N/A (Reel 19, Frame 16)
      Dates of Confessions: 13/12/1976
    - Chun Chhum, 15/3/1977 (Reel 21, Frame 35)
      Dates of Confessions: 18/3/1977; 2/3/1977; 8/3/1977; 1 section undated
    - Chun Chrak, N/A (Reel 7, Frame 15)
    - Chun Chroeuk, 26/8/1975 (Reel 13, Frame 31)
      Dates of Confessions: 5/9/1975; 23/12/1975
    - Chun Thoeurn, 9/1976 (Reel 22, Frame 15)
      Dates of Confessions: 10/2/1977; 11/2/1977; 13/2/1977; 14/2/1977; 15/2/1977; 16/2/1977; 10/2/1977; 11/2/1977
      13/2/1977; 13/2/1977; 15/2/1977; 16/2/1977
    - Chung Kim, 28/1/1978 (Reel 7, Frame 19)
      Dates of Confessions: 31/3 78; 7/4/1978
    - Chung Kim, 31/3/1978 (Reel 23, Frame 7)
      Dates of Confessions: 31/3/1978; 5/4/1978
    - Chung Pharop, 21/5/1977 (Reel 13, Frame 4)
      Dates of Confessions: 26/8/1977
    - Chunn Sok Nguon, 19/10/79 (Reel 5, Frame 7)
      Dates of Confessions: 7/11/1976; 10/11/1976; 11/11/1976; 12/11/1976; 7/12/1976; 15/11/1976; 18/11/1976
      18/11/1976; 18/11/1976; 28/10/1976; 23/1076; 6/11/1976; 19/10/1976
      15/11/1976; 21/10/1976
    - Chuon Am, N/A (Reel 23, Frame 31)
      Dates of Confessions: 5/8/1977
    - Chuon Chea, 1/7/1978 (Reel 19, Frame 20)
      Dates of Confessions: 7/8/1978; 12/7/1978
    - Chuon Chhon, 10/12/1975 (Reel 5, Frame 4)
      Dates of Confessions: 13/9/1975; 17/12/1975
    - Chuon Heng, 19/3/1977 (Reel 16, Frame 18)
      Dates of Confessions: 24/2/1977; 26/2/1977; 3/3/1977; 9/3/1977(2)
    - Chuon Koeurn, N/A (Reel 16, Frame 21)
      Dates of Confessions: 30/8/1977
    - Chuon Luy, 2/1978 (Reel 23, Frame 2)
    - Chuon Nuon, N/A (Reel 22, Frame 6)
    - Chuon Uon, N/A (Reel 14, Frame 14)
      Dates of Confessions: 17/7/1977; 19/7/1977; 15 sections undated
    - Chuon Van Vy, N/A (Reel 7, Frame 5)
    - Chuon Vanny, 8/12/1976 (Reel 19, Frame 7)
      Dates of Confessions: 30/1/1977; 31/1/1977; 1/2/1977; 10/2/1977; 5/2/1977; 9/2/1977; 1/2/1977; 30/1/1977
      31/1/1977; 3/2/1977; 4/2/1977/; 7/2/1977; 3/1/1977; 9/2/1977
      4/2/1977; 5/2/1977; 3/2/1977(2)
    - Chuon Vuon, 30/8/1976 (Reel 14, Frame 3)
    - Chuong Pheng, 9/10/1975 (Reel 21, Frame 15)
      Dates of Confessions: 1/1/1975
    - Chuong Sarun, 6/1/1977 (Reel 7, Frame 4)
      Dates of Confessions: 1/3/1977
    - Chuong Sarun, 6/1/1977 (Reel 20, Frame 36)
    - Chuop Hin, 9/1977 (Reel 19, Frame 32)
    - Chuop Lim, 11/6/1977 (Reel 21, Frame 24)
    - Chuop Neam, N/A (Reel 6, Frame 7)
      Dates of Confessions: 26/6/1977
    - Chuop Vantha, 29/9/1977 (Reel 11, Frame 2)
      Dates of Confessions: 12/10/1977
    - Chuor Chan Sarik, 6/1977 (Reel 18, Frame 35)
      Dates of Confessions: 21/10/1977; 5/10/1977
    - Chuor Sovan Han, 12/10/1976 (Reel 12, Frame 16)
      Dates of Confessions: 18/10/1976; 11/11/1976; 12/11/1976; 14/11/1976; 15/11/1976; 16/11/1976
      21/11/1976; 22/11/1976; 23/11/1976; 24/11/1976; 27/11/1976; 28/11/1976
      29/11/1976; 30/11/1976; 2/12/1976; 3/12/1976; 4/12/1976; 5/12/1976
      6/12/1976; 7/12/1976; 8/12/1976; 9/12/1976; 10/12/1976; 11/1276; 12/12/1976
    - Chy Chiv, 24/8/1977 (Reel 18, Frame 1)
      Dates of Confessions: 27/8/1977; 4/10/1977; 6/10/1977
    - Courtigne Andre, N/A (Reel 19, Frame 25)
  - Names: D
    - Daing Yaing Phou (Phon), 7/2/1976 (Reel 187, Frame 32)
    - Daing Yaing Thann, 21/5/1976 (Reel 187, Frame 16)
    - Dam Chhaen, 1/1/1978 (Reel 26, Frame 5)
      Age: 57
    - Dam Chhat, 31/1/1978 (Reel 26, Frame 4)
    - Dam Rong, 29/3/1977 (Reel 24, Frame 23)
      Dates of Confessions: 22/5/1977; 1 section undated
    - Dam Say, N/A (Reel 23, Frame 33)
      Dates of Confessions: 26/2/1977
    - Dam Sem, N/A (Reel 23, Frame 32)
      Dates of Confessions: 7/3/1977; 8/3/1977
    - Dam Torn, 12/7/1976 (Reel 25, Frame 13)
      Dates of Confessions: 11/1/1978
    - Dan Chan Leng, 11/6/1978 (Reel 26, Frame 20)
    - Danch Heng, 11/11/1976 (Reel 23, Frame 34)
      Dates of Confessions: 30/11/1976; 1/12/1976; 2/12/1976; 3/12/1976; 4/12/1976; 5/12/1976; 6/12/1976; 7/12/1976; 8/12/1976; 9/12/1976; 11/12/1976
    - Danch Sy Yan, N/A (Reel 24, Frame 12)
    - Dang Dinh Yung [Dany Dinh (Dung) Yung (Bao Dony Yang)], 20/3/1978 (Reel 187, Frame 50)
    - Dang Vann Kaon, 4/12/1978 (Reel 186, Frame 115)
    - Daung Davuth, N/A (Reel 24, Frame 24)
      Dates of Confessions: 25/8/1976; 25/9/1976; 21/8/1976; 26/9/1976; 29/9/1976; 28/9/1976; 25/9/1976; 21/9/1976; 26/9/1976; 30/9/1976; 29/9/1976; 24/9/1976; 29/9/1976; 7/10/1976
    - Daung Nop, N/A (Reel 24, Frame 1)
    - Daung Phuon, N/A (Reel 25, Frame 4)
    - Daung Reth, 24/2/1977 (Reel 26, Frame 27)
      Dates of Confessions: 28/2/1978
    - Daung Sreng, N/A (Reel 24, Frame 14)
      Dates of Confessions: 9/8/1976; 24/9/1976; 25/9/1976; 27/9/1976
    - David Lloyd Scott, N/A (Reel 185, Frame 53)
      Dates of Confessions: 12/12/1978; 26/12/1978
      Nationality (if foreign): CIA/Australia Intelligence
    - De Ceng Khanh (Do Long Khanh), 28/2/1978 (Reel 186, Frame 46)
    - Deang Phika, 6/10/1976 (Reel 24, Frame 31)
      Dates of Confessions: 28/10/1976; 29/10/1976; 31/10/1976; 1/11/1976(2); 6/11/1976; 7/11/1976; 9/11/1976; 18/10/1976
    - Deap Nang, N/A (Reel 25, Frame 10)
      Dates of Confessions: 7/6/1977
    - Deap Peou, N/A (Reel 24, Frame 30)
      Dates of Confessions: 6/8/1977
    - Deap Sim, 6/10/1977 (Reel 25, Frame 8)
      Dates of Confessions: 5/12/1977; 1 section undated
    - Deap Yan, 11/7/1976 (Reel 26, Frame 11)
      Dates of Confessions: 30/8/1976; 31/8/1976; 1/9/1976
    - Dek, 27/2/1977 (Reel 26, Frame 1)
      Dates of Confessions: 9/3/1977
    - Dek Dey, N/A (Reel 23, Frame 36)
      Dates of Confessions: 11/May
    - Dek In, 23/1/1977 (Reel 26, Frame 15)
      Dates of Confessions: 21/1/1977; 22/1/1977; 23/1/1977
    - Den (Pen) Nen Yim, 25/12/1975 (Reel 185, Frame 27)
      Nationality (if foreign): Roong Island
    - Deng Nang, N/A (Reel 24, Frame 22)
      Dates of Confessions: 2/11/1977(2); 16/10/1977; 29/10/1977; 4 sections undated
    - Deng Uy, 12/11/1977 (Reel 24, Frame 17)
    - Deup Rim, 14/1/1977 (Reel 24, Frame 3)
      Dates of Confessions: 1/12/1977
    - Diah (Dinh) Van Phan, 29/8/1978 (Reel 187, Frame 45)
    - Dim Khom, N/A (Reel 24, Frame 25)
    - Dim Samith, 19/7/1977 (Reel 26, Frame 2)
    - Dim Saroeurn, 21/7/1977 (Reel 26, Frame 3)
    - Din Yaing Phoeng, 27/7/1978 (Reel 187, Frame 19)
    - Dinh Van Phat, 27/7/79 (Reel 187, Frame 40)
    - Dith Kong, N/A (Reel 24, Frame 8)
      Dates of Confessions: 1/6/1977
    - Do Kong Nam (Do Rong Nam), 18/9/1978 (Reel 186, Frame 2)
    - Do Van Phou, 22/4/1978 (Reel 186, Frame 66)
    - Do Van Tong, 22/4/1978 (Reel 186, Frame 67)
    - Doam (Daam) Van Kath, 18/6/1978 (Reel 187, Frame 72)
    - Doek Phat, 2/2/1978 (Reel 26, Frame 22)
    - Doeuk Soth, 16/12/1977 (Reel 25, Frame 15)
    - Doeur Prak, N/A (Reel 23, Frame 38)
      Dates of Confessions: 31/8/1975; 4/9/1975; 5/9/1975; 7/9/1975; 8/9/1975; 9/9/1975; 12/10/1975; 13/10/1975; 15/10/1975; 18/10/1975; 15/11/1975; 1 section unclear
    - Doeur Um, 4/6/1978 (Reel 24, Frame 15)
    - Doeur Veng, 6/12/1976 (Reel 26, Frame 19)
      Dates of Confessions: 30/1/1977; 31/1/1977; 1/2/1977 ;2/2/1977; 3/2/1977; 4/2/1977; 5/2/1977; 6/2/1977; 8/2/1977; 9/2/1977;10/2/1977; 11/2/1977; 11/2/1977
      13/2/1977;14/2/1977; 15/2/1977; 16/2/1977; 17/2/1977;18/2/1977; 19/2/1977
      20/2/1977; 21/2/1977
    - Doeurk Pheach, N/A (Reel 25, Frame 2)
      Dates of Confessions: 16/9/9/1977; 19/9/1977; 20/9/1977; 17/10/1977; 31/10/1977; 6/11/1977
    - Dok Choeurn, N/A (Reel 25, Frame 9)
    - Dom Koeurn, 18/1/1978 (Reel 26, Frame 8)
      Dates of Confessions: 18/1/1978
    - Dom Mut, 6/2/1978 (Reel 26, Frame 26)
      Dates of Confessions: 15/2/1978
    - Dom Sear, 1/6/1978 (Reel 24, Frame 18)
    - Don Chleam, 26/11/1977 (Reel 26, Frame 12)
      Dates of Confessions: 5/2/1978; 11/2/1978
    - Dop Yun, 31/8/1976 (Reel 24, Frame 16)
      Dates of Confessions: 7/9/1976(3); 9/9/1976; 10/9/1976(2); 12/9/1976(2); 18/9/1976
    - Dos Lim, 2/8/1977 (Reel 26, Frame 23)
    - Douk Ruth, 5/6/1977 (Reel 26, Frame 21)
      Dates of Confessions: 2/8/1977; 29/8/1977; 5/9/1977; 9/9/1977; 11/9/1977; 20/9/1977; 23/9/1977; 3/10/1977; 4/10/1977; 25/9/1977
    - Dourng Pheng, 10/10/1975 (Reel 24, Frame 29)
      Dates of Confessions: 22/2/1976; 23/2/1976; 30/10/1975
    - Duam Loek, 8/1977 (Reel 25, Frame 6)
      Dates of Confessions: 9/8/1977; 9/1977
    - Duang Kim Leng, N/A (Reel 24, Frame 5)
    - Duch Bun, N/A (Reel 24, Frame 28)
      Dates of Confessions: 18/7/1977
    - Duch Kean, 21/10/1976 (Reel 24, Frame 19)
    - Duch Phat, N/A (Reel 24, Frame 9)
      Dates of Confessions: 23/5/1977
    - Duch Tan, 30/12/1977 (Reel 24, Frame 20)
      Dates of Confessions: 7/6/1978
    - Duch Thel, 4/1977 (Reel 26, Frame 9)
      Dates of Confessions: 26/6/1977; 3/7/1977; 10/7/1977
    - Duk Sambo, 24/7/1977 (Reel 24, Frame 27)
    - Dul Chhum, 3/12/1978 (Reel 26, Frame 13)
      Dates of Confessions: 26/11/1978
    - Dul Lan, N/A (Reel 24, Frame 26)
    - Duong Bopha, N/A (Reel 23, Frame 37)
      Dates of Confessions: 7/12/1976; 8/12/1976; 10/1/1977; 11/1/1976; 12/1/1977; 13/1/1977; 14/1/1977; 15/1/1977; 16/1/1977; 17/1/1977
      21/1/1977; 22/1/1977; 23/1/1977
    - Duong Chi, 5/1/1976 (Reel 25, Frame 11)
    - Duong Khoeurn, N/A (Reel 24, Frame 11)
    - Duong Sakhan, 21/4/1976 (Reel 24, Frame 21)
    - Duong Sam, 4/9/1976 (Reel 24, Frame 13)
      Dates of Confessions: 11/10/1976; 15/10/1976; 16/10/1976; 17/10/1976; 18/10/1976; 20/10/1976; 22/10/1976; 23/10/1976
    - Duong Saran, 8/1977 (Reel 26, Frame 6)
    - Duong Treng, 1/7/1978 (Reel 25, Frame 16)
      Dates of Confessions: 5/7/1978; 7/7/1978
    - Duong Uom, 22/2/1978 (Reel 26, Frame 29)
      Dates of Confessions: 22/2/1978
    - Duong Van, 14/8/1976 (Reel 24, Frame 32)
      Dates of Confessions: 3/8/1976; 14/8/1976; 9/7/1976; 14/8/1976; 18/7/1976; 10/7/1976; 8/8/1976; 13/8/1976
    - Duong Yoeurn, 1/1978 (Reel 26, Frame 7)
    - Dup Dara, 19/12/1976 (Reel 26, Frame 16)
      Dates of Confessions: 17/12/1976; 18/12/1976; 19/12/1976; 22/12/1976
    - Durng Sareth, 13/1/1977 (Reel 26, Frame 10)
      Dates of Confessions: 7/2/1977; 14/2/1977; 15/2/1977
    - Dy Ath, N/A (Reel 24, Frame 7)
      Dates of Confessions: 11/5/1977
    - Dy Bun Long, 29/7/1976 (Reel 25, Frame 14)
      Dates of Confessions: 18/8/1976(10); 22/8/1976; 11/9/1976(7); 12/9/1976(2); 17 sections undated
    - Dy Chak, 6/2/1978 (Reel 26, Frame 25)
    - Dy Chamruern, 8/1977 (Reel 25, Frame 1)
    - Dy Cheng, N/A (Reel 24, Frame 2)
      Dates of Confessions: 6/3/1978
    - Dy Chhan, N/A (Reel 24, Frame 4)
      Dates of Confessions: 2/4/1977; 3/4/1977; 4/4/1977; 5/4/1977; 9/3/1977; 10/3/1977(3); 11/3/1977; 12/3/1977; 13/4/1977(2)
      14/3/1977; 15/3/1977; 16/3/1977; 18/3/1977; 19/3/1977(2); 20/3/1977; 21/3/1977
      22/3/1977; 23/3/1977; /24/3/1977; 25/3/1977; 26/3/1977; 27/3/1977; 28/3/1977
      29/3/1977; 30/3/1977; 31/3/1977; 1/4/1977; 5/4/1977
    - Dy Leng, 3/10/1977 (Reel 26, Frame 17)
      Dates of Confessions: 17/10/1977; 23/10/1977; 25/10/1977
    - Dy Moeurn, 15/1/1978 (Reel 25, Frame 12)
      Dates of Confessions: 25/6/1978
    - Dy Phally, 18/7/1976 (Reel 25, Frame 3)
    - Dy Phon, 13/12/1978 (Reel 26, Frame 14)
      Age: 48
      Dates of Confessions: 13/12/1978; 14/12/1978; 15/12/1978; 16/12/1978; 17/12/1978; 18/12/1978; 19/12/1978; 20/12/1978
    - Dy Rat, 26/5/1977 (Reel 26, Frame 28)
    - Dy Samin, 9/2/1978 (Reel 26, Frame 24)
      Dates of Confessions: 14/2/1978
    - Dy Sarom, N/A (Reel 23, Frame 35)
      Dates of Confessions: 3/1/1976
    - Dy Simorn, 4/1/1978 (Reel 25, Frame 7)
      Dates of Confessions: 16/1/1977; 13/2/1978; 31/1/1978
    - Dy Tha, 9/2/1977 (Reel 24, Frame 6)
      Dates of Confessions: 13/2/1977; 14/2/1977; 15/2/1977
  - Names: E
    - E Che, N/A (Reel 26, Frame 32)
      Dates of Confessions: 21/6/1977
    - E Kim San, N/A (Reel 28, Frame 5)
      Dates of Confessions: 25/2/1977
    - E Sik, 20/7/1978 (Reel 29, Frame 9)
      Dates of Confessions: 7/9/1979
    - Eak Lun, N/A (Reel 29, Frame 2)
    - Eam Chan, N/A (Reel 28, Frame 7)
      Dates of Confessions: 22/2/1978; 4/2/1978; 8/3/1978
    - Eam Kheum, 1/3/1977 (Reel 29, Frame 19)
      Dates of Confessions: 11/3/1977; 12/3/1977; 13/3/1977; 14/3/1977; 15/3/1977; 16/3/1977(3); 17/3/1977
    - Eam Khon, 17/3/1977 (Reel 29, Frame 18)
      Dates of Confessions: 8/10/1976
    - Eam Korn, 13/9/1975 (Reel 27, Frame 11)
      Dates of Confessions: 13/10/1975; 19/10/1975; 1 section undated
    - Eam Ron, N/A (Reel 29, Frame 3)
      Dates of Confessions: 22/3/1978
    - Eam Sarun, 5/3/1978 (Reel 29, Frame 8)
      Dates of Confessions: 5/3/1978
    - Eam Sokha, 18/2/1978 (Reel 27, Frame 20)
      Dates of Confessions: 25/3/1978
    - Ean Hun, 25/1/1978 (Reel 29, Frame 21)
      Dates of Confessions: 9/8/1977
    - Eang Chung Kheng, 11/1977 (Reel 29, Frame 1)
    - Eang Dim, 17/3/1977 (Reel 29, Frame 17)
      Dates of Confessions: 4/8/1977; 5/8/1977
    - Eang Heang, 26/6/1978 (Reel 29, Frame 16)
      Dates of Confessions: 2/7/1978
    - Eang Lan, 22/9/1976 (Reel 27, Frame 18)
      Dates of Confessions: 26/1/1977(2); 3/11/1976; 31/10/1976; 7/10/1976; 6/10/1976; 4/10/1976; 5/10/1976; 8/10/1976
      31/10/1976; 29/10/1976; 5/10/1976; 4/10/1976; 8/10/1976; 5/10/1976; 2/11/1976
      23/10/1976; 17/10/1976
    - Eang Man, N/A (Reel 27, Frame 16)
    - Eang Moeurn, 7/12/1978 (Reel 28, Frame 10)
      Dates of Confessions: 30/12/1978
    - Eang Neng, 9/8/1976 (Reel 29, Frame 13)
    - Eang Song, 30/5/1976 (Reel 26, Frame 34)
    - Eang Suntery, N/A (Reel 29, Frame 23)
      Dates of Confessions: 6/10/1975; 27/9/1975
    - Eang Than, 14/3/1977 (Reel 27, Frame 4)
    - Ear Chamroeurn, 8/1977 (Reel 29, Frame 7)
      Age: 16
      Dates of Confessions: 29/12/1977
    - Ear Choeu, 16/2/1977 (Reel 27, Frame 15)
      Dates of Confessions: 6/3/1977; 10/3/1977; 14/3/1977; 8/4/1977; 11/4/1977; 1 section undated
    - Ear Hor, 10/11/1975 (Reel 28, Frame 12)
    - Ear Nay Prong, 10/12/1978 (Reel 27, Frame 3)
      Dates of Confessions: 27/12/1978
    - Ear Puth, N/A (Reel 27, Frame 22)
      Dates of Confessions: 18/9/1976(6); 19/9/1976(3); 20/9/1976
    - Ear Saroeurn, 1/9/1978 (Reel 28, Frame 15)
      Dates of Confessions: 21/9/1978
    - Earn Kunneary, 12/1976 (Reel 26, Frame 33)
      Dates of Confessions: 4/12/1976; 17/12/1976; 25/12/1976
    - Eat Bun Ly, 27/6/1977 (Reel 29, Frame 4)
      Dates of Confessions: 27/6/1977